haivision.com 2014-10-19

# | Haivision | Enterprise Video Solutions

**Privacy Policy last updated June 12th, 2012.**

Haivision is committed to protecting your privacy and ensures compliance with all applicable privacy laws and statutes. Please read the Haivision Online Privacy Policy below.  This Online Privacy Policy applies to data collected by Haivision through its Web site and services, as well as its offline support services.

 **Collection of Your Personal Information**  
A unique ID may be assigned to you that will be used to identify your credentials and associated information. We ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. 

While we may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the Haivision site and services as well as certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses, this information is not linked to any identifiable personal information.  Haivision may set and access cookies in order to assist such collection.

 **Use of Your Personal Information**  
Haivision collects and uses your information to operate and improve its site and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the site or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.  Haivision does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Haivision nonetheless discovers that it has received personally identifiable information from an individual who is (or who Haivision has reason to believe is) under the age of 13, Haivision will delete such information from its systems

Haivision, its affiliates, and subsidiaries may also use your personal information to communicate with you and may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Haivision, its affiliates, and subsidiaries may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Haivision and its partners.

Personal information collected through Haivision sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Haivision or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a Haivision site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Haivision abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

 **Sharing of Your Personal Information**  
Except as described in this statement, or when disclosure is required by law (as in response to a subpoena or governmental investigation), we will not disclose your personal information outside of Haivision and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent.

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.  
Haivision reserves the right to modify this "Privacy Policy" at any. We encourage you to check this page from time to time for any modifications/updates.
